We're swaying on horseback
The hills are green
And the birdies sing
And roses are pink
Experience I never had
I'm so happy
Happy to just be part of your story
After you I follow
The world you show me broaden my horizon
Forever my hero
I am your biggest fan
Merry-go-round
In a circle I run
It's so much fun leaving reality behind
I fall down the horseback
With my crippled legs
And then it starts to rain
Showing me it's all fake
Raindrops wash down the facade
Hills are painted
Birdies are robotic
Roses are made of clay
Excitement that I feel
Return them to the shelf
Cause now I understand
Heroes cannot be real
I wasn't who I am
I don't know who I am
¿Who am I?
Here we go, another lap
Prizes to claim
Here's a dream for you
Here's a dream for me
Golden tickets in my bag stay unexchanged
Don't you love the thrill of the chase?
Just let me be your fan
I wanna be your fan
I'm still your biggest fan
Why is it that some were given the role of villian
The moment they were released into this system?
Stand up
Gallop on
Nothing can be done by feeling so sorry for myself
Hero
On a plastic horse
Fighting like it's real
With a cardboard sword
I know
Successful or not, I am who I am
I am my biggest fan
I am my enemy and my friend
Hero
Gonna prove my version of justice
Is more just than yours
Uno
Remaining on this stage, I am the only one
I am my biggest fan
I am my enemy and my friend